<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ubucon Europe 2022</title><link>https://2022.ubucon.org/</link><description>Recent content on Ubucon Europe 2022</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://2022.ubucon.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ubucon Europe 2022 - Looking for volunteers!</title><link>https://2022.ubucon.org/news/2022-01-24-looking-for-volunteers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://2022.ubucon.org/news/2022-01-24-looking-for-volunteers/</guid><description>Hello everyone!
After a successful Ubucon Europe in 2019, we have been lacking in organizing another one.
This is mostly due to the taxing of the pandemic, on which we were waiting to see if we could at some point do an in-person event. At the pace of how things are developing in the world, right now, an in-person event doesn’t seem a viable thing to do without major risks and hassles, hence we decided to do it online.</description></item><item><title>Closing session</title><link>https://2022.ubucon.org/sessions/closing_session/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 19:50:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://2022.ubucon.org/sessions/closing_session/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s wrap up this year&amp;rsquo;s 2 days the Ubucon Europe! And see you on next year!(Maybe in-person?)</description></item><item><title>Welcome and Opening Remarks</title><link>https://2022.ubucon.org/sessions/welcome_and_opening_remarks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 13:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://2022.ubucon.org/sessions/welcome_and_opening_remarks/</guid><description>This session will cover how and why we have organized the UbuCon Europe event. We&amp;rsquo;ll also introduce our host organizing communities, sponsors and partner communities.
About the speaker Something</description></item><item><title>About Ubucon Europe 2022</title><link>https://2022.ubucon.org/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://2022.ubucon.org/about/</guid><description>Welcome, and thank you for your interest on Ubucon Europe.
This event is being organized. If you want to be part of the event, feel free to join our Jitsi at our next meeting, or send an e-mail in case you want to volunteer but don’t want/can’t join the Jitsi. Details below:
URL: https://quentinho.ubcasts.com/StartUbucon2022 When: 12th February 2022. E-mail: 2022@ubucon.eu</description></item><item><title>Become a sponsor</title><link>https://2022.ubucon.org/sponsors/become-a-sponsor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://2022.ubucon.org/sponsors/become-a-sponsor/</guid><description>Thank you for your interest in Ubuntu and Ubucon Asia.
As a non-profit and community organized event, Even Ubucon Asia 2021 is fully virtual event, We still need support from sponsors to make the event happen.
By becoming one of our sponsors, you are directly contributing to research and development of Ubuntu and Open Source Software, and also making Open Source Community more active and sustainable.
Your contribution makes it possible for us to bring a large number of Ubuntu users and contributors across Asia to connect, interact, help and learn together.</description></item><item><title>Join as Partner Community</title><link>https://2022.ubucon.org/sponsors/join-as-partner-community/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://2022.ubucon.org/sponsors/join-as-partner-community/</guid><description>To promote UbuCon Asia event across Asia much further, We’re looking for partner communities. By becoming our partner community, Your community will collaborate with UbuCon Asia team to cross-promote each other’s community and event. This will be a big help for both partner communities and UbuCon Asia to connect with even more diverse people and encourage them to participate and engage.
To learn more about our partner community program, please refer to our brochure.</description></item><item><title>Ubuntu Portugal Local Community</title><link>https://2022.ubucon.org/hosts/ubuntu-pt/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://2022.ubucon.org/hosts/ubuntu-pt/</guid><description>Welcome to Ubuntu Portugal! The Ubuntu Portugal Local Community (Ubuntu-PT) is the Portuguese community for the GNU/Linux distribution Ubuntu. This community is made of volunteers which helps promoting the usage of Ubuntu and free software as well, but also helping Portuguese users.
Para mais informações ou contactos:
website: https://ubuntu-pt.org/ telegram: &amp;ldquo;https://t.me/ubuntuptgeral&amp;quot; facebook: &amp;ldquo;https://www.facebook.com/ubuntuportugal&amp;quot; grupo facebook: &amp;ldquo;https://www.facebook.com/groups/ubuntupt&amp;quot; irc: #ubuntu-pt @ irc.freenode.net</description></item><item><title>Virtual Venue (Gather town)</title><link>https://2022.ubucon.org/venue/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://2022.ubucon.org/venue/</guid><description>For Sponsor &amp;amp; Partner Community Virtual booth and To Socialize Attendees, We have Gather space for the event. Hope you enjoy our Gather space, meet new people and also make new opportunities!
Entering Gather space &amp;amp; Going back to Eventyay To join Gather space, Join the event room on eventyay first, Then click &amp;ldquo;Gather.town space&amp;rdquo; on sidebar. That brings you to Gather space. To go back to eventyay video call, You may find dedicated areas for going back to eventyay.</description></item></channel></rss>